

Curriculum Vitae

PERSONAL

Name: Rumil Christian T. Seloveres

Address: Purok-1 Estaca, Pilar, Bohol Zipcode: 6321

Phone number: 09661552780 (Globe)/ 09923777336 (Dito)

Email: rumil.christian@gmail.com

Date of birth: 24-10-2000

Place of birth: Tagbilaran City

Gender: Male

Nationality: **Filipino**Marital status: **Single**

RESUME OBJECTIVE

I'm Rumil Christian T. Seloveres, 23 years of age studying at the University of Bohol with the course of Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering. To undergo On-the-Job-Training (OJT) to enhance my competence and gain relevant and practical industrial skills pertaining to my course taken. I can create a software program using Java programming language and I assure you that I'm the person you want in your company.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Mar 2017 – May 2017 Sales Clerk

Alturas Group of Companies, Tagbilaran City

A sales clerk in the Alturas Mall.

Dec 2018 – Jan 2019 Work Immersion

LGU - Pilar, Municipality of Pilar, Pilar, Bohol Encoder and Assistant Computer Technician

June 2019 – April 2020 Student Assistant/Working Scholar

University of Bohol, Tagbilaran City

Assistant Encoder, Cleaner

EDUCATION

2012 - 2013 Grade 1 - Grade 6

Estaca Elementary School, Estaca, Pilar, Bohol

2013 - 2017 Grade 7 - Grade 10 High School

Pilar Technical-Vocational High School, Poblacion Pilar

2017 - 2019 Grade 11 - Grade 12 Senior High School

Pilar Technical-Vocational High School, Poblacion Pilar

2019 – 2024 (Present) Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering (BSCOMPE)

University of Bohol, Tagbilaran City

REFERENCES

Engr. Liduvina Namocatcat Instructor

Email: llnamocatcat@gmail.com, Cell: +63 (0) 995 907 6922

Engr. Victor John Anunciado Instructor

Email: vjlanunciado@universityofbohol.edu.ph, Cell: 63 (0) 945

480 9029

SKILLS

Java Software Developer, AutoCAD 2D & 3D Designing, Proteus 8 Professional PCB Development

Experienced

CERTIFICATES/WORKSHOPS AND SEMINARS ATTENDED:

June 10, 2016	Community - Based Computer Literacy Course - TESDA
March 22, 2019	Computer Systems Servicing - NCII, TESDA
April 18, 2022	For Builders: Create Tomorrow - COMPESA Seminar
November 12, 2022	It Starts with Us: Challenge Yourself - COMPESA Seminar
December 01, 2022	Eagle CAD: PCB Design and Development - COMPESA Seminar
December 09, 2022	First COMFESTA 2022
January 2023	Emergency First Aid Training
May 20, 2023	Demystifying Innovation V1.0: Bridging the Gap Between Ideas and Implementation - COMPESA Seminar
June 22, 2023	National ICT Month ICT Learning and Certification Summit - Department of Information and Communication Technology Diliman Quezon City
September 16, 2023	MATLAB Onramp - MathWorks Training Services
September 2023	Seminar on PhilNITS Certification Exams
October 2-3, 2023	BHL i2i - Panda Tea Garden Suites, Tagbilaran City
October 2023	Top 25 Regional Finalists in the 8 th Annual Philippine Startup Challenge - 18 th Place with "Cradletalk"
October 2023	Webinar on Quantum Computing Lecture Series and Hackathon
December 09, 2023	3D Printing Design - COMFESTA 2023
December 09, 2023	Sumobot Competition, 2 nd Runner Up - COMFESTA 2023
December 09, 2023	Sumobot Competition - COMFESTA 2023

I hereby certify that the above-mentioned information is true and correct to the best of my knowledge.